IntelliJ IDEA can significantly reduce the amount of typing you have to do while coding,
IntelliJ IDEA可以显着减少编码时的输入量，
in this screencast we're going to look at how.
在此截屏视频中，我们将研究如何操作。
We'll start with a plain no-frills Java project,
我们将从简单的Java项目开始，
so we can see how much work IntelliJ IDEA can do for us from an empty start.
因此我们可以从一开始就看到IntelliJ IDEA可以为我们做多少工作。
There's a more detailed look at getting started with a new project in another screencast.
在另一个截屏视频中，将详细介绍如何开始新项目。
We're also going to use the keyboard for
我们还将使用键盘进行
the majority of our navigation, as demonstrated in the Navigation screencast.
我们的大部分导航，如“导航”截屏中所示。
IntelliJ IDEA has created a source directory
IntelliJ IDEA已创建源目录
for our production Java code, but we need to create a directory for our test code.
用于我们的生产Java代码，但是我们需要为我们的测试代码创建一个目录。
We can use Alt Insert on Windows or Cmd N on Mac to create something new.
我们可以在Windows上使用Alt Insert或在Mac上使用Cmd N来创建新内容。
Here in the project window, we're going to create a new directory.
在项目窗口中，我们将创建一个新目录。
We need to tell IntelliJ IDEA this is for test code, so we can right click and mark
我们需要告诉IntelliJ IDEA这是测试代码，因此我们可以右键单击并标记
it as a test directory.
将其作为测试目录。
Now we have the basic directories, we can
现在我们有了基本目录，我们可以
create our Java packages.
创建我们的Java包。
Typing in the "new" dropdown lets us narrow down the options to the ones we want.
输入“新”下拉菜单可让我们将选项缩小到所需的范围。
We can type the full package name here, and IntelliJ IDEA will create the correct directory
我们可以在此处键入完整的软件包名称，IntelliJ IDEA将创建正确的目录
structure for this package.
该程序包的结构。
Now we have a package, we can create a new
现在我们有了一个包，我们可以创建一个新的
Java class.
Java类。
In this first example we're going to create a simple Main class.
在第一个示例中，我们将创建一个简单的Main类。
You can see IntelliJ IDEA creates a Main.java file with the appropriate package and class
您可以看到IntelliJ IDEA使用适当的包和类创建了Main.java文件。
declaration already filled in.
声明已填写。
Next, we can use a feature called Live Templates
接下来，我们可以使用称为实时模板的功能
to create standard template code without having to type much.
创建标准模板代码而无需键入太多内容。
We type psvm and press tab or enter, and IntelliJ IDEA creates a public static void main method
我们输入psvm并按tab或Enter，然后IntelliJ IDEA创建一个公共static void main方法
for the class and places our cursor in the method body.
类，然后将光标放在方法主体中。
There are a lot of live templates for generating
有很多实时模板可用于生成
common code.
通用代码。
If we want to print something to System.out we can type sout and again we have a number
如果要打印一些内容到System.out，我们可以输入sout，然后再次输入一个数字
of options.
选项。
We'll select the simplest option, and print the String "Hello".
我们将选择最简单的选项，并打印字符串“ Hello”。
Running the class gives us the output we expect.
运行该类将为我们提供期望的输出。
---
---
That's just a taste of how IntelliJ IDEA can
那只是IntelliJ IDEA可以尝到的味道
help us while we're coding.
在编码时帮助我们。
Let’s look at a slightly more realistic example.
让我们看一个更现实的例子。
We're going to use a Test Driven Development approach to create some basic Shape functionality.
我们将使用“测试驱动开发”方法来创建一些基本的Shape功能。
Firstly we'll use Alt + Ins / Cmd + N again
首先，我们将再次使用Alt + Ins / Cmd + N
to create a new class.
创建一个新类。
When we have our skeleton class, we can use Alt and Enter on the class name and select
当我们有了骨架类时，可以在类名上使用Alt和Enter键，然后选择
Create Test to create a Unit test for this class.
创建测试以为此类创建一个单元测试。
IntelliJ IDEA supports a number of standard testing libraries out of the box, we're going
IntelliJ IDEA开箱即用地支持许多标准测试库，我们将
to use Junit 5 for our tests.
使用Junit 5进行测试。
The IDE tells us we don't have the JUnit 5 Jar files on the classpath, and we can use
IDE告诉我们在类路径上没有JUnit 5 Jar文件，我们可以使用
the Fix button to download the libraries from Maven central and put them on the classpath
修复按钮以从Maven Central下载库并将其放在类路径中
so they're available for us to use.
因此它们可供我们使用。
We have the option to generate some of the structure of the test class, but we don't
我们可以选择生成测试类的某些结构，但是我们没有
need to for these examples.
需要这些例子。
IntelliJ IDEA adds Assertions as a static
IntelliJ IDEA将断言添加为静态
import to make it as easy as possible for use to write tests that compile straight away.
import使其尽可能容易地用于编写直接编译的测试。
The IDE has created this test file in the test sources root in the appropriate package,
IDE已在相应程序包的测试源根目录中创建了此测试文件，
creating all the appropriate directory structure for us.
为我们创建所有适当的目录结构。
We can use generate again to create a new
我们可以再次使用generate来创建一个新的
test method.
测试方法。
This is annotated with the Junit 5 annotation, and IntelliJ IDEA expects us to change the
这是用Junit 5注释注释的，IntelliJ IDEA希望我们更改
method name to something more meaningful, and on pressing Enter our cursor is placed
方法名称更有意义，然后按Enter键
inside the method body.
在方法主体内部。
IntelliJ IDEA offers a number of different
IntelliJ IDEA提供了许多不同的选择
types of code completion that can help us as we create the test.
可以帮助我们创建测试的代码完成类型。
Various options are offered by default as we type, we don't even need to use a shortcut
默认情况下，键入时会提供各种选项，我们甚至不需要使用快捷方式
to bring up the suggestions.
提出建议。
Suggestions are not just for types, but are even made for variable names.
建议不仅针对类型，甚至针对变量名称。
We can provoke suggestions by using Ctrl and Space, which gives us basic completion.
我们可以使用Ctrl和Space来提出建议，这使我们有了基本的完成。
This generally shows a wide range of possibilities that might work in the current location.
这通常显示在当前位置可能起作用的各种可能性。
Using Shift Ctrl Space invokes Smart Completion.
使用Shift Ctrl Space可以调用智能完成。
This is type-aware and only suggests options that are the correct type for the context.
这是类型识别的，仅建议与上下文正确类型的选项。
In this case, we only had one type that fitted, so IntelliJ IDEA automatically selected Square
在这种情况下，我们只能安装一种类型，因此IntelliJ IDEA会自动选择Square
for us.
为了我们。
Typing a dot will bring up the list of available
键入一个点将弹出可用列表
options on a symbol.
符号上的选项。
If we want to create some new functionality on this class, we can choose to ignore what's
如果我们要在此类上创建一些新功能，则可以选择忽略
there already and define our new method name.
在那里并定义我们的新方法名称。
The editor will warn us that this method doesn't exist, but if we press Alt and Enter on this
编辑器将警告我们该方法不存在，但是如果我们按Alt并按Enter
red method we can choose to create this missing method.
红色方法，我们可以选择创建此丢失的方法。
IntelliJ IDEA can use the information we've already provided to create the method structure.
IntelliJ IDEA可以使用我们已经提供的信息来创建方法结构。
For example this method returns an int because in the test we assign the result of calling
例如，此方法返回一个int，因为在测试中我们分配了调用结果
this method to an int variable.
此方法为int变量。
In the spirit of test driven development,
本着测试驱动开发的精神，
we'll leave this as the simplest thing that compiles and go back to the test.
我们将其保留为最简单的编译方法，然后返回测试。
Now we can define what we expect the result to be.
现在我们可以定义期望的结果。
Note that IntelliJ IDEA's code completion suggestions can work on partial method names
请注意，IntelliJ IDEA的代码完成建议可以对部分方法名称起作用
and camel case to make it easier to find the method we need with minimal typing and minimal
和骆驼的情况下，以最少的打字和最少的工作量，更轻松地找到我们所需的方法
risk of misspelling.
拼写错误的风险。
When we run the test we see it fails, but
当我们运行测试时，我们看到它失败了，但是
this is expected.
这是预期的。
Let's go back to the implementation and make the simplest change that will fix the test.
让我们回到实现并进行最简单的更改以修复测试。
Now we have a passing test, we can safely refactor the code.
现在我们已经通过了测试，可以安全地重构代码。
For example here we might want to move this hardcoded value into a field.
例如，在这里我们可能想要将此硬编码的值移动到字段中。
We can initialise the value in the current method, in the field declaration, or in the
我们可以在当前方法，字段声明中或在
constructor.
构造函数。
We can also uses Alt and Enter to see options for changing where we initialise it if we
我们还可以使用Alt和Enter键来查看用于更改初始化位置的选项
want to.
想要。
There are other screencasts which go into refactoring in more depth, here we've seen
还有其他一些截屏视频可以更深入地进行重构，在这里我们已经看到了
a taste of how we can use it to automatically generate the code we want.
了解如何使用它来自动生成所需的代码。
We can use refactoring to generate new files
我们可以使用重构来生成新文件
for us as well.
对我们也一样。
For example, now we have the Square class we might want to create a Shape interface
例如，现在我们有了Square类，我们可能想创建一个Shape接口
for it to implement.
实施。
Here I'm using Find Action to call Extract Interface.
在这里，我使用“查找操作”来调用“提取接口”。
Let's create an interface called Shape, and add the getNumberOfSides method to it.
让我们创建一个名为Shape的接口，并向其中添加getNumberOfSides方法。
We're not going to replace the current usages of Square with Shape, but we could if we wanted
我们不会用Shape替换Square的当前用法，但是如果我们愿意，我们可以
to.
至。
We can see intelliJ IDEA has updated Square to implement our new Shape interface, and
我们可以看到，IntelliJ IDEA已经更新了Square以实现我们的新Shape接口，并且
added the Override annotation to getNumberOfSides.
在OverNumber注释中添加了getNumberOfSides。
We can see our Shape interface is straightforward.
我们可以看到Shape界面很简单。
Let's create a new type of Shape.
让我们创建一种新型的Shape。
This time we're going to create the test class before we create the class it is testing.
这次，我们将在创建要测试的类之前先创建测试类。
Again we can generate our test method and call it something appropriate.
同样，我们可以生成我们的测试方法，并对其进行适当的调用。
We can define a Shape local variable, this time we want it to be a new type, Polygon.
我们可以定义一个Shape局部变量，这一次我们希望它是一个新的类型Polygon。
IntelliJ IDEA lets us create this new class using Alt Enter, and places it into the correct
IntelliJ IDEA使我们可以使用Alt Enter创建此新类，并将其放入正确的位置。
directory.
目录。
Because we are using this from a Shape variable, IntelliJ IDEA correctly assumes we want this
因为我们在Shape变量中使用它，所以IntelliJ IDEA正确地假设我们想要这个
polygon to implement our Shape interface.
多边形来实现我们的Shape接口。
The editor is showing an error since Polygon doesn't implement the Shape methods yet, we
编辑器显示错误，因为Polygon尚未实现Shape方法，我们
can use Alt and Enter again and select Implement Methods to fix this problem.
可以再次使用Alt和Enter并选择“实施方法”来解决此问题。
As usual we can accept the simplest implementation that compiles in order to continue writing
与往常一样，我们可以接受最简单的编译实现以继续编写
our test.
我们的测试。
In the test, we can continue coding to create
在测试中，我们可以继续编码以创建
the API we want and getting IntelliJ IDEA to make the changes we need.
我们想要的API，并使IntelliJ IDEA做出我们需要的更改。
The IDE can create fields for constructor parameters that aren't currently being used.
IDE可以为当前未使用的构造函数参数创建字段。
Once again, now the code compiles we can define our test expectations….
再次，现在代码可以编译，我们可以定义我们的测试期望…。
And re-run the test.
并重新运行测试。
Of course it fails, so we return the numberOfSides field value from the method and see the test
当然它会失败，因此我们从方法中返回numberOfSides字段值并查看测试
passing as expected.
通过预期。
Often domain objects like this require some
像这样的领域对象通常需要一些
standard methods.
标准方法。
We can get IntelliJ IDEA to generate these methods for us.
我们可以使IntelliJ IDEA为我们生成这些方法。
For example, we can generate a toString method, defining which fields should be included.
例如，我们可以生成一个toString方法，定义应包括哪些字段。
There are a number of templates we can use to create the method, depending upon which
我们可以使用许多模板来创建方法，具体取决于哪个
standard approach we want to choose.
我们要选择的标准方法。
Generated methods are usually placed wherever the caret was.
生成的方法通常放置在插入符号所在的位置。
Let's use the same process to generate the equals and hashCode methods.
让我们使用相同的过程来生成equals和hashCode方法。
Again, we have options for the way we want the generated method to work.
同样，对于希望生成的方法起作用的方式，我们有一些选择。
We can choose which fields to include in the equals method, and which to use in hashCode.
我们可以选择在equals方法中包括哪些字段，以及在hashCode中使用哪些字段。
While having these methods in a class, and
在类中使用这些方法时，以及
even generating them like this, is quite standard for Java programmers, it can lead to a bit
即使生成这样的代码，对于Java程序员来说也是相当标准的，这可能会导致
of noise and mess in our domain objects.
域对象中的噪音和混乱。
Sometimes we want clear organisation of our code in order to understand, for example,
有时候，我们想要清楚地组织代码，以了解例如
which are generated methods and which are business logic.
哪些是生成的方法，哪些是业务逻辑。
We can apply consistent organisation to our classes by automatically rearranging our code.
通过自动重新排列代码，我们可以将一致的组织应用于班级。
Here I'm going to use Find Action to search for Rearrange code and to apply it to this
在这里，我将使用“查找动作”来搜索重新排列代码并将其应用于此
class.
类。
Here we’re using the default settings for code organisation, which has placed the constructor
在这里，我们使用代码组织的默认设置，该默认设置用于放置构造函数
at the top of the class, would put any inner classes at the bottom of the file, and will
在类的顶部，将所有内部类放在文件的底部，并将
organise fields, for example grouping static fields together.
组织字段，例如将静态字段分组在一起。
We can change the existing settings to suit
我们可以更改现有设置以适合
our needs, or even add our own rules.
我们的需求，甚至添加我们自己的规则。
For example, I would like all my getter methods to be below any other methods that might contain
例如，我希望我的所有getter方法都位于可能包含的任何其他方法之下
business logic, since the getters are not as important to see.
业务逻辑，因为获取者并不那么重要。
Note that we can use regular expressions to define a pattern for method name.
注意，我们可以使用正则表达式为方法名称定义模式。
Even less important than the getters are the other generated methods, so let's create a
比生成器更重要的是其他生成的方法，所以让我们创建一个
rule to put them underneath all the other types of methods.
将它们置于所有其他类型方法之下的规则。
Now when we re-arrange the code, the getter is put above the other generated methods.
现在，当我们重新排列代码时，将getter置于其他生成的方法之上。
Now we have our basic domain object in place
现在我们有了基本的领域对象
let's create some more business logic and see how code generation and code completion
让我们创建更多的业务逻辑，看看代码生成和代码完成的方式
helps us here.
在这里帮助我们。
We continue to use the test to drive the design
我们继续使用测试来驱动设计
of the API.
API。
For this functionality, it makes sense that we'll pass in to the Polygon constructor some
对于此功能，有意义的是，我们将传递给Polygon构造函数一些
sort of array or collection that contains the lengths of all the sides in the polygon.
包含多边形中所有边的长度的一种数组或集合。
Here I'm going to use postfix completion to define the variable.
在这里，我将使用后缀补全来定义变量。
IntelliJ IDEA offers a range of postfix completion options to help generate common code, press
IntelliJ IDEA提供了一系列后缀完成选项来帮助生成通用代码，请按
the up arrow on the completion list to see all the ones that are available for the current
完成列表上的向上箭头可查看当前可用的所有
context.
上下文。
We'll use var to create a local variable for this Polygon.
我们将使用var为该Polygon创建局部变量。
When creating variables, we don't have to accept the default type, we can press Shift
创建变量时，我们不必接受默认类型，可以按Shift键。
and Tab to put the focus on the type and see which options are available.
和Tab键将焦点放在类型上，并查看可用的选项。
For this example I don't want to define it with the Shape interface, but with the Polygon
对于此示例，我不想使用Shape接口定义它，而是使用Polygon定义它
class itself.
类本身。
This constructor doesn't exist yet, so IntelliJ
此构造函数尚不存在，因此IntelliJ
IDEA gives us the option to either modify the existing constructor, or to create another
IDEA为我们提供了修改现有构造函数或创建另一个构造函数的选项
constructor.
构造函数。
If we choose to modify the existing constructor we'll see the Change Signature dialog which
如果选择修改现有的构造函数，则会看到“更改签名”对话框，其中
lets us customises the method to our needs.
让我们根据需要定制方法。
We already have a test that uses the existing constructor, so for now we're going to create
我们已经有一个使用现有构造函数的测试，因此现在我们将创建
a new constructor that meets the needs of this test.
满足此测试需求的新构造函数。
We can always refactor later.
我们以后总是可以重构。
We should do something with both parameters
我们应该同时使用两个参数
to the new constructor.
到新的构造函数。
IntelliJ IDEA recognises that there's a field that matches the name of the first constructor
IntelliJ IDEA识别出一个字段与第一个构造函数的名称匹配
parameter, so we can get it to generate the code to assign this parameter to the correct
参数，因此我们可以获取它来生成代码以将该参数分配给正确的参数
field.
领域。
The second parameter doesn't have a field yet, so we'll get IntelliJ IDEA to create
第二个参数还没有字段，因此我们将使用IntelliJ IDEA创建
it for us.
对我们来说。
We've created this as a final field, but it hasn't been initalised in the field or
我们已将其创建为最终字段，但尚未在该字段中初始化
in the original constructor.
在原始的构造函数中。
We'll get IntelliJ IDEA to initialise this field to a zero length array in the original
我们将获得IntelliJ IDEA将该字段初始化为原始数组中的零长度数组
constructor.
构造函数。
Now the code compiles, we can go ahead and
现在代码已编译，我们可以继续
write the rest of the logic for the test.
编写测试的其余逻辑。
Note that code completion doesn't require us to type much at all, especially for methods
请注意，代码完成完全不需要我们输入太多，尤其是对于方法
we've already called in this class.
我们已经在这一堂课中打电话了。
Again, we can use smart completion to suggest the methods that return a type that's compatible
同样，我们可以使用智能补全功能来建议返回兼容类型的方法
with this method, but we don't have the method we need yet, so let's define its name in this
使用此方法，但是我们还没有所需的方法，因此让我们在此定义它的名称
test and created it using Alt and Enter again.
测试并使用Alt和Enter再次创建。
We can choose whether the method belongs on the interface or the implementation, for now
现在，我们可以选择方法是属于接口还是实现
we'll put it on the implementation as we only need it on Polygon right now, we can refactor
我们将其放在实现上，因为现在我们只需要在Polygon上使用它，我们就可以重构
it later if we need to.
如果需要的话，稍后再说。
Once again we want to choose the simplest code that works and see the test turn red.
再次，我们想选择最简单的代码，然后看到测试变成红色。
Now we'r going to implement the logic to make
现在，我们将执行逻辑以使
the test pass.
测试通过。
We're going to want to iterate over our sideLengths field.
我们将要遍历sideLengths字段。
Iteration is another example of standard code that we can generate.
迭代是我们可以生成的标准代码的另一个示例。
For example, we could use postfix completion again, in this case the key for iterating
例如，我们可以再次使用后缀完成，在这种情况下，迭代的密钥
is "iter".
是“ iter”。
This will generate a standard foreach to iterate over the array.
这将生成一个标准的foreach来遍历数组。
Alternatively there are a number of different Live Templates for iteration.
或者，有许多不同的实时模板可用于迭代。
We could select "itar", which creates a classic for loop to iterate over the array.
我们可以选择“ itar”，它创建了一个经典的for循环来遍历数组。
Or we can use "iter" to create a foreach loop.
或者我们可以使用“ iter”创建一个foreach循环。
We'll create a simple check to assign the
我们将创建一个简单的检查来分配
longest value we find to the local variable longest.
我们找到的最长值为局部变量的最长值。
We can use quick fixes to make our code compile where necessary.
我们可以使用快速修复程序在必要时使我们的代码编译。
Now we have our business logic, we'll re-run the test to see if it passes, which it does.
现在我们有了业务逻辑，我们将重新运行测试以查看其是否通过。
Now we have a passing test, we can refactor
现在我们已经通过了测试，我们可以重构
our code safely knowing we can always run the test to make sure it still passes.
我们的代码安全地知道我们可以始终运行测试以确保它仍然可以通过。
For example, we could use the Java 8 inspections to automatically convert this for loop into
例如，我们可以使用Java 8检查来自动将此for循环转换为
a Streams API call.
Streams API调用。
Re-running the test shows this gives the same result as the previous code.
重新运行测试表明，此结果与先前的代码相同。
I personally find Streams calls easier to
我个人发现Streams通话更容易
read if each method is on a separate line.
读取每个方法是否在单独的行上。
Let's select this code and use Alt + Enter to adjust how the code is formatted.
让我们选择此代码，然后使用Alt + Enter调整代码的格式。
This settings dialog shows just the settings that apply to the selected piece of code.
此设置对话框仅显示适用于所选代码段的设置。
We're going to select Wrap Always on Chained Method Calls, you can see the editor previews
我们将选择“始终在链式方法调用上包装”，您可以看到编辑器预览
the formatting changes without us needing to save them.
格式更改无需我们保存。
We can select Save if we're happy with these settings.
如果我们对这些设置感到满意，可以选择“保存”。
Now the code is formatted this way, I can
现在以这种方式格式化代码，我可以
see the filter criteria more clearly.
更清楚地查看过滤条件。
I have a theory that we don't need this filter, since the max method alone will give us what
我有一个理论，我们不需要此过滤器，因为仅max方法会给我们带来什么
we need.
我们需要。
Let's delete this line and re-run the test to make sure it all still works.
让我们删除此行，然后重新运行测试以确保所有功能仍然有效。
Which it does!
哪有！
Finally let's call re-arrange code again to
最后，让我们再次调用重新排列代码以
make sure the newly generated method is in the right place.
确保新生成的方法在正确的位置。
We've used IntelliJ IDEA's code generation
我们已经使用了IntelliJ IDEA的代码生成
to create standard Java code, so we don't have to type in the code we sometimes refer
创建标准的Java代码，因此我们不必键入有时引用的代码
to as boilerplate.
作为样板。
We've also used the different types of code completion to help us to write the code we
我们还使用了不同类型的代码完成功能来帮助我们编写代码
need, again reducing the typing required and allowing us to focus on the actual problems
需要，再次减少了所需的打字，使我们能够专注于实际问题
we're trying to solve.
我们正在努力解决。
Thanks for watching!
感谢收看！